I was saying that I really tried to give realization to all those [inaudible]  me, in fact, [inaudible]
Ben, bana [duyulmuyor] olan herkese gerçekten aydınlanma vermeye çalıştığımı söylüyordum, aslında [duyulmuyor]
Americans can't say. I can do my level best. [inaudible] with the proof. All right. [inaudible]
Amerikalılar söyleyemez. Elimden gelenin en iyisini yapabilirim. [duyulmuyor]  kanıtla. Tamam. [duyulmuyor]
[inaudible] too much money, don't know what to do with yourself, now when they say, "I'm suffering". Otherwise you can't enjoy.[inaudible]
[duyulmuyor] çok para, ne yapacağını bilemiyorsun, Şimdi "acı çekiyorum" diyorlar. Aksi takdirde zevk alamazsın. [duyulmuyor]
You are really making me self conscious now [inaudible]
Şimdi Beni gerçekten utandırıyorsun [duyulmuyor]
I like the Rockefella center, its really [inaudible].
Rockefellar merkezini seviyorum, gerçekten [duyulmuyor].
What is this one? This is also a building? this has very bad [vibrations? inaudible].
Bu nedir? Bu da bir bina mı? Bu çok kötü [vibrasyonlar- duyulmuyor].
Why everyone is not having a family? nothing? They have [inaudible] They have go on to have no culture
Neden herkesin bir ailesi yok? Hiçbir şey yok mu? Onların [duyulmuyor,] Onların kültürü yok
they murder people.
insanları öldürüyorlar.
[inaudible] I think they have a right to do what they [want? inaudible]
[duyulmuyor] Bence istediklerini yapma hakları var [istiyorlar mı? -uyulmuyor]
[inaudible] can't stay here longer. [inaudible] will run away.
[duyulmuyor] burada daha fazla kalamam. [duyulmuyor] kaçacak.
He never comes to Manhattan. [inaudible]
Manhattan'a asla gelmez. [duyulmuyor]
story is about the advent of the primordial one, that, the deity of Brahma, Vishnu, Mahesha, you know who they are.
hikayesi, Ezeli olanın, Brahma  Vishnu, Mahesha, Deitylerinin kim olduklarını biliyorsunuz.
Their wife, their power
Eşleri, güçleri
fell jealous of a lady who was very pure, Anushuiya.
çok saf bir kadın olan Anushuiya'yı kıskandılar.
She is the power of the primordial, I mean she was the mother. She's the mother of all the Gurus.
O, Ezeli olanın gücüdür, yani O bir anne idi. O, tüm Guru'ların annesidir.
And they said that she, this lady is such a chaste lady and too much [inaudible] and make her fall from her chastity [inaudible] her.
Ve dediler ki, bu kadın çok iffetli bir kadın ve çok [duyulmuyor] ve onu iffetinden düşürün [duyulmuyor].
She was actually the primordial mother Anusiya. So they went into her house, she was a wife of a very big Saint and he was out.
O aslında Ezeli anne olan Anusiya idi. Onlar onun evine gittiler, o çok büyük bir azizin karısıydı ve kocası dışarıdaydı.
And they said, "we want .." See, a guest who comes to your house can demand anything, according to Indian dharma. So they came in and then said that
Ve dediler ki, "biz şunu istiyoruz..." Bakın, Hint dharmasına göre, evinize gelen bir misafir her şeyi talep edebilir. Onlar içeri girdiler ve dediler ki,
"We want you to serve our food naked. Take out all your clothes and [serve us?]"
"Bizim yemeğimizi bize çıplak olarak servis etmeni istiyoruz. Bütün giysilerini çıkar ve [bize servis yap?]"
Now you can't say no to your guests because that is your dharma. "It's all right, I will do it.",she said
Artık misafirlerine hayır diyemezsin çünkü bu senin dharma'n. "Tamam, yapacağım." dedi
[inaudible] but as soon as she started, [both of them?] became little children. [inaudible]
[duyulmuyor] ama o başlar başlamaz, [ikisi de?] küçük çocuklar oldular. [duyulmuyor]
Little little babies.
Küçük bebekler.
[inaudible] And the little baby doesn't understand anything and she nursed them together.
[duyulmuyor] Ve küçük bebekler hiçbir şeyden anlamıyorlardı ve o onları birlikte emzirdi.
All right. And then she said, "Now."
Tamam. Sonra "Şimdi" dedi.
She combined them together, and that's how Dattatrieya, has three faces. Innocence of these people.
Onları birleştirdi ve Dattatrieya'nın üç yüzü böyle oluştu. Bu insanların masumiyetidir.
She brought them to their innocence. The innocence was created, and this is the innocence of these three deities [Christ is the innocence? inaudible].
Onları masumiyetlerine kavuşturdu. Masumiyet yaratıldı ve bu, bu üç Deity’nin masumiyetidir [Mesih masumiyet midir? duyulmuyor].
These three form this innocence part to balance and this state they come, here as [inaudible], innocence has latent power [inaudible] ekadesha rudra.
Bu üçü, dengeyi sağlamak için bu masumiyet kısmını oluşturur ve bu duruma, buraya [duyulmuyor], masumiyet gizli bir güce sahiptir [duyulmuyor] ekadesha rudra.
I mean there are [inaudible] way but others are also powers of [inaudible].
Demek istediğim, [duyulmuyor] yolu var ama diğerleri de [duyulmuyor] güçleridir.
That's how they establish [inaudible]. All that is in the void and come here at [this side?]
İşte böyle [duyulmuyor] kurarlar. Her şey Void’dadır ve buraya [bu tarafa?] gelir.
See this hand, and left, this is Ganesha, the innocence part.
Bu eli görün, ve sol, bu Ganesha, masumiyet kısmı.
That, all right?
Tamam mı?
I mean I don't know how, how one should have [reached this sthiti?] and Jains are the [inaudible] in India.
Yani, nasıl, nasıl birinin [bu sthiti'ye ulaşması gerektiğini bilmiyorum?] ve Jainler Hindistan'da [duyulmuyor]'dır.
These Jains, you see, are strict people, very strict vegetarianism they have, they don't even eat garlic. [inaudible] Garlic is very important for the heart, they don't eat garlic, they don't eat onion.
Bu Jainler, görüyorsunuz, katı insanlardır, çok katı vejeteryanlardır, sarımsak bile yemezler. [duyulmuyor] Sarımsak kalp için çok önemlidir, onlar sarımsak yemezler, soğan yemezler.
The whole thing revolves around [food ?], they are strict vegetarian but [inaudible] got realization [inaudible] he was a jain and his wife was a pure jain and he hated all that non sense.
Her şey [yemek ?] etrafında döner, onlar katı vejeteryanlardır ama [duyulmuyor] aydınlanmaya ulaştı [duyulmuyor] o bir Jain'di ve karısı? da saf bir Jain'di ve o tüm bu saçmalıklardan nefret ediyordu.
So, he told me "I was Jain." [inaudible] Because they are told not to eat meat or anything, what they do when they come to America?
Bana "Ben Jain'dim" dedi. [duyulmuyor] Çünkü onlara et ya da başka bir şey yememeleri söylenir, Amerika'ya geldiklerinde ne yaparlar?
They go to all the youth clubs, they drink a lot, the only thing that they don't eat is [inaudible?].
Tüm gençlik kulüplerine giderler, çok içki içerler, yemedikleri tek şey [duyulmuyor?].
They are rich people, they are very rich and [inaudible]. And same with the Jews, you can find.
Zengin insanlardır, çok zengindirler ve [duyulmuyor]. Yahudilerde de aynı şeyi görebilirsiniz.
The religion is limited to a little part, the rest is [inaudible]. I mean [inaudible] not with any commandments.
Din küçük bir kısmıyla sınırlıdır, geri kalanı [duyulmuyor]. Yani [duyulmuyor] herhangi bir emir yok.
What can you do about it? I mean, [they have become more sensible now? [inaudible], fanaticism is a very very collective ego,
Bu konuda ne yapabilirsiniz? Yani, [şimdi daha mantıklı hale geldiler mi? [duyulmuyor], fanatizm çok çok kolektif bir egodur,
I think, its a very big collective ego,
bence, çok büyük bir kolektif egodur,
the collective ego is [inaudible] and when collective become [inaudible], you start loving you know,
kolektif ego [duyulmuyor] ve kolektif [duyulmuyor] olduğunda, sevmeye başlarsınız, bilirsiniz,
like English people, they [inaudible] by using spoons and forks.
İngilizler gibi, onlar [duyulmuyor] kaşık ve çatal kullanarak.
According to them, those who cannot use spoons and forks are [not English?].
Onlara göre, kaşık ve çatal kullanamayanlar [İngiliz değil mi?].
That's how they feel about it.
Onlar böyle düşünüyorlar.
I have landed in America.
Amerika'ya indim.
[inaudible] of some house property.
[duyulmuyor] bir ev mülkü.
How does she remember all that, I am surprised, its a good memory.
Bütün bunları nasıl hatırlıyor, şaşırdım, iyi bir hafızası var.